[{"answer": "You're kiddin'!  Alright!  I'll be there around two or three", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't know.  Warm stuff, I guess. It's the mountains.  I guess it gets cold at night.  I'm just gonna bring everything", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We don't need the lantern.  The place has electricity", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "In case of what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's my friend's, the day manager's.  He's gettin' a divorce, so his wife's gettin' this place, so he's just lettin' all his friends use it till he has to turn over the keys", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How come he let you go", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, my friend.  I know you're all upset.  It's just I'm so excited to be out of the house, I guess.  I wonder if my friend's home yet", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why don't you tell him to just to get lost once and for all", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Shouldn't we go to the cops?  I mean, I think we should tell the police", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know.  Just tell 'em what happened", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " We have to think this through.  We have to be smart.  Now is not the time to panic.  If we panic now, we're done for.  Nobody saw it. Nobody knows it was us.  We're still okay.  Now all we have to do is just figure out our next move", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "If you weren't so concerned with having a good time, we wouldn't be here right now", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " What the fuck is going on", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Of course.  Of course!  Where?  Can't I bring it to you?  For God's sake, baby, please, just tell me what's happened, what could possibly be so bad", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Not yet", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Can't it go to any office", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Tell me now", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Okay.  I'll call you back.  In an hour.  Don't tell my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Call me back", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I know.  Call me back.  my friend, I love you, okay", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I've been tellin' you that for the last ten years", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't think my friend is mature enough to conduct an affair", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Friend of mine, owns a club.  my friend.  You'd know him if you saw him.  His brother was in your class. my friend", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "  No, honey.  I told him I was buyin' a car.  What is it for", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Call him.  Don't tell him anything. Tell him you're having a wonderful time and you'll be home tomorrow night", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know.  I won't be", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Well, it looks like we can get on this road 81 that heads down towards that place, then cut over to..", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Wait.  What?  You want to go to that place from that place and you don't want to go through that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " I don't want to go that way.  Find a way that we don't have to go through that place", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You know how I feel about that place... We're not going that way", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, that's my husband, he says he's not ready.  He's still too much of a kid himself.  He prides himself on being infantile", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "my friend and my friend don't get along", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What did ya do", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You're a bank robber", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I'm a robber", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Nope.  I've never robbed a bank", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, please get a hold of yourself. You're making a spectacle", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm sorry.  I am happy.  I'm very happy for you.  I'm glad you had a good time.  It's about time.  Where is he now", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Oooooweee!!  You shoulda seen me! Like I'd been doin' it all my life! Nobody would ever believe it", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Maybe.  Maybe.  The call of the wild", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " my friend?  Where are we", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " that place", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Just past that place", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " that place, my friend.  We're crossing into that place", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " that place", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " I always wanted to see that place", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I guess I always thought the worst thing that could happen would be to end up old and alone in some crummy apartment with one of those little dogs", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You know those little dogs you see people with", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Gosh.  It sure is", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Well, you got it now", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What?  What's not funny, my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Front", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "As far as I'm concerned, yes, ma'am, you are", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I think I've really fucked up.  I think I've got us in a situation where we could both get killed.  Why didn't we just go straight to the police", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "What'd I say again", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "That guy was hurtin' me.  And if you hadn't come out when you did, he'd a hurt me a lot worse.  And probably nothin' woulda happened to him. 'Cause everybody did see me dancin' with him all night.  And they woulda made out like I asked for it.  And my life woulda been ruined a whole lot worse than it is now.  At least now I'm havin' fun.  And I'm not sorry the son of a bitch is dead.  I'm only sorry that it was you that did it and not me.  And if I haven't, I wanna take this time to thank you, my friend.  Thank you for savin' my ass", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "No, my friend, you said the first part. I said all the rest", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No, my friend.  I'm not gonna make any deals", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes!  Yes!  Now what kind of deal do you think that cop can come up with to beat that", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "It would have to be pretty damn good", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Yeah.  I been seein' you, too", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What are you talkin' about", "docId": "thelmaandlouise.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Go", "qsentId": 66}]